--- Testing DGIC Unavailable (Invalid Hash) ---
Result: ABSTAIN, Reason: DGIC snapshot rejected: DGIC_SEAL_VERIFICATION_FAILED: Cryptographic seal verification failed: Cryptographic seal broken: envelope_hash does not match payload hash. ENVELOPE TAMPERED.

--- Testing RAJYA Unavailable ---

--- Testing Core Unavailable ---
Exception propagated: Core execution failed

--- Testing Trace Mismatch (Execution ID Mismatch) ---
Result: ALLOW, Reason: None

--- Testing Contract Mismatch ---
Contract failure caught: ValidationError - 1 validation error for KSMLInput
metadata
  Value error, KSML metadata missing required canonical fi

--- Testing Replay Validation ---
Verified 0 bucket entries.
